Hey. Let me join you.
Nobody wants to play with me
Forget it.Forget it.
I'm often lonely
Oh. Go to Shizuka's home.
Shizuka
Sorry. I've got to do something. Talk to you later.
Shizuka, wait.
Shizuka, wait...
Don't forget me when you go to America.
OK. See you.
I feel very happy to stay with you.
I don't know when I will come back to Japan
Stop that
We're always good friends even we're separate
Right?
Yes.
This is souvenir for you
Thank you. Shizuka
I'll write to you when I go to America
Do remember. So do I
His friend moves
It'll be lonely
If I move away
you'll feel lonely
Take care.
See you.
Hey. Hey.
Actually I'll move to America too
Don't make such joke at this time
Shizuka
Hey. Hey. Everybody.
I've something important to tell you.
What's the matter?
What? What?
I'll move to America
America!
Right
That's OK
There's no some strange man, this place will become better
That's not important
It's too much... That's all, in either case I...
We're not serious
I don't know
Let's have a try
Hypothetic box
Well, it's very nice to have this
If...
If I move to America...
I'm coming, I'm coming...
Hey, Yebi, how are you?
Ah, darling
What? Will you move to America?
Is there your company in America either?
No, but I have to move there
It's very toilsome
Nobita, Doraemon, father will move to America
Make prepare to move quickly
OK...
Go to tell them quickly
Nobita, it's better to transmit that
That's almost
I don't know whom the first one is
Who's coming?
She must be Shizuka
Suneo
Really? Nobita, will you move to America?
Yes
Really...
Ouch! Ouch...
I'll be lonely
Be careful!
Don't let those rogues tease you in America
If you're not used to live there, you may come back
Don't forget me
And I...
Nobita...
It's really surprised! How could Suneo cry?
Me too
She's coming
She's must be Shizuka
Giant
will you go to America?
Yes
I remembered the past
I was not kind
even I teased you on purpose...
I feel maybe you hate me
and think I'm a boring guy
Please forgive me...
I know
I've not hated you
Really?
Really
Thanks, I'm glad to hear that
This's souvenir, here you are
Take it
Wait... I can't accept it
No, if you don't accept it, I'll feel sad
Wait, Giant...
Don't destroy it
You may return it to him later
It must be Shizuka this time
We take the place of our classmates to come here
We'll hold up Nobita's farewell in the school tomorrow
Troublesome... it's too troublesome
This... that...
That's all, so troublesome
No, nothing
I won't give up
before Shizuka comes here
Nobita, will you go to America?
Yes
You must be firm there
Don't make Japan to be shameful
If you can't speak English, it'll be very troublesome
I'll send you English tape
You'd recite before you start out
I'll test you every day, see you
Will you play any longer?
No, get back the original state as soon as possible
Oops, aren't you Shizuka?
What's the matter? Shizuka, why are you here?
Come in please
Well... will you really move to America?
Yes
In a word, come in first
Shizuka, I've been waiting for you
Will you move to America?
It's really too sudden
I---
How to say...
Shizuka
I... because I...
How cruel
Get back the original state quickly
Strange...
Doraemon, there's no ring
What're you saying?
There's really something wrong
Oops... what's the matter...
What shall I do?
If it's not repaired, I really move to America
No! No!
I don't want to America
Me too
Can't it be repaired?
I don't know
This's present
Thanks, then I'll take it
Hasn't it been repaired?
It's useless to urge
Uncle in Hokkaido
Come to send me off
Doraemon, hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
It's not so fast, this machine is very tangle some
I've not finished my talk
It's unnecessary
Then I can't set my heart at rest
Please follow me to come out
Come! Beat me!
I... I often teased you before
I'm really sorry
Beat me please! I beg you
If you don't beat me, I won't be comfortable
I feel uncomfortable
You said so, but...
Beat me quickly
Beat me!
Yes!
Come on!
Hey, what's that?
Energize!
I know
If you're not serious, I won't be polite
Come on quickly!
I'll beat you
That's all
It's repaired
Come! Suneo
Get back the original state
Sorry, Suneo
Nobita, why do you beat me?
Why? Suneo
Wait!
How could I be sad?
Sorry, Suneo, Shizuka Giant, everyone...
Thanks...